<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <title>Intro</title>
    <skit artist="puffDaddy" theme = "none">
        <line>Push</line>
        <line>C'mon, shorty, stay push, c'mon</line>
        <line>C'mon, c'mon, push it's almost there</line>
        <line>One more time, c'mon</line> 
        <line>C'mon, push, baby, one more time</line> 
        <line>Harder, harder, push it harder</line> 
        <line>Push, push, c'mon</line> 
        <line>One more time, here it goes</line> 
        <line>I see the head!</line> 
        <line>Yeah, c'mon!</line> 
        <line>Yeah! Yeah!</line> 
        <line>You did it, baby, yeah!</line>
    </skit>

    <interlude artist="biggie" theme = "none">
        <line>But if you lose, don't ask no questions why</line> 
        <line><style type = "hyperbole">The only game you know is do or die</style></line>
        <line>Ah-ha-ha</line> 
        <line>Hard to understand what a hell of a man...</line> 
        <line>Hip hop the hippie the hippie</line> 
        <line>To the hip hip hop and you don't stop</line> 
        <line>Rock it out, baby bubba, to the boogie, the bang-bang</line> 
        <line>The boogie to the boogie that be</line> 
        <line>Now, what you hear is not a test...</line>
    </interlude>

    <skit artist="princeCharlesAlexander" theme = "none">
        <line>God damn it, Voletta, what the fuck are you doin'?</line> 
        <line>You can't control that God damn boy? What?</line> 
        <line>I just saw Mr. Johnson, he told me he caught the motherfucking boy shoplifting</line> 
        <line>What the fuck are you doin'? <adlib>Get your black ass the fuck off!</adlib></line>
        <line>You can't control that God—</line> 
        <line>I don't know what the fuck to do with that boy</line>
        <line>What the fuck do you want me to do?</line> 
        <line>If— if you can't con— fucking control him</line>
        <line>I'ma send him— <adlib>All you fucking do is bitch all day, motherfucker</adlib></line>
        <line>I'ma send him— Bitch, bitch, I—</line> 
        <line>I'ma send his motherfuckin' ass to a group home</line> 
        <line>God damn it, what? I'll smack the shit outta you, bitch! <adlib>Kick my black ass, motherfucker!</adlib></line> 
        <line>What the fuck?</line> 
        <line>Yo— You— You are fucking up <adlib>Comin' in here, smellin' like sour socks, you dumb motherfucker</adlib></line> 
        <line>I'ma fuck you up</line>
    </skit>

    <interlude artist="biggie" theme = "none">
        <line>When I'm bustin' up a party I feel no guilt</line>
        <line>Gizmo's cuttin' up for thee</line> 
        <line>Suckers that's down with nei—</line>
    </interlude>
    
    <skit artist="biggie" theme = "wealth">
        <line>What, nigga, you wanna rob them motherfuckin' trains, you crazy?</line>
        <line>Yes, yes, motherfucker, motherfuckin' right, nigga, yes</line>
        <line>Nigga, what the fuck, nigga? We gonna get—</line> 
        <line>Nigga, it's eighty-seven nigga, is you dead broke?</line> 
        <line>Yeah, nigga, but, but, nigga—</line> 
        <line>Motherfucker, is you broke, motherfucker?</line> 
        <line>We need to get some motherfuckin' paper, nigga</line> 
        <line>Yeah, but nigga, it's a train, ain't nobody robbed no motherfucking train</line> 
        <line>Just listen, man, your mother giving you money, nigga?</line> 
        <line>My moms don't give me shit, nigga</line> 
        <line>It's time to get paid, nigga</line>
        <line>Is you with me?</line>
        <line>Motherfucker, is you with me?</line> 
        <line>Yeah, I'm with you, nigga, c'mon</line> 
        <line>Alright then, nigga, let's make it happen then</line> 
        <line>All you motherfuckers get on the fuckin' floor!</line> 
        <line>Get on the motherfucking floor!</line> 
        <line>Give me all your motherfucking money <adlib>And don't move, nigga!</adlib></line>
        <line>I want the fuckin' jewelry, give me every-fuckin'-thing</line> 
        <line>Nigga I'd shut the fuck up or I'ma blow your motherfuckin' brains out! (Gimme your fuckin' money, motherfucker!)</line>
        <line>Nigga, give me your jewelry, empty your pockets (Fuck you, bitch)</line> 
        <line>Get up off that shit</line> 
        <line>What the fuck you holding on to that shit for, bitch?</line>
    </skit>

    <interlude artist="biggie" theme = "none">
        <line>I get money, money I got</line> 
        <line>Stunts call me honey if they feel real hot</line>
    </interlude>

    <skit artist="biggie" theme = "none">
        <line>Open C-74, Smalls</line> 
        <line>Mr. Smalls, let me walk you to the door</line> 
        <line>So how does it feel leaving us?</line>
        <line>C'mon man, what kind of fucking question is that man?</line> 
        <line>Trying to get the fuck up out this joint dog</line> 
        <line>Yeah, yeah, you'll be back</line> 
        <line>You niggers always are</line> 
        <line>Go ahead man, what the fuck is you hollering about?</line> 
        <line>You won't see me up in this motherfucker no more</line> 
        <line>We'll see I got big plans nigga, big plans, hahahaha</line>
    </skit>
</song>
