<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
    [Intro: Notorious B.I.G.]
    Yeah, motherfuckers better know
    Huh, huh (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Lock your windows, close your doors
    Biggie Smalls
    Huh, yeah
    (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    
    [Verse 1]
    My man Inf left a TEC and a nine at my crib
    Turned him self in, he had to do a bid
    A one-to-three, he be home the end of '93
    I'm ready to get this paper, G, you with me?
    Motherfuckin' right, my pockets lookin' kinda tight
    And I'm stressed
    Yo, Biggie let me get the vest
    No need for that, just grab the fuckin' gat
    The first pocket that's fat, the TEC is to his back
    Word is bond, I'ma smoke him, yo, don't fake no moves (What?)
    Treat it like boxin', stick and move, stick and move
    Nigga, you ain't got to explain shit
    I've been robbin' motherfuckers since the slave ships
    With the same clip and the same four-five
    Two point blank, a motherfucker sure to die
    That's my word, nigga even try to bogard
    Have his mother singin', "It's so hard"
    Yes, love, love your fuckin' attitude
    Because the nigga play pussy
    That's the nigga that's gettin' screwed
    And bruised up from the pistol whippin'
    Welts on the neck from the necklace strippin'
    Then I'm dippin' up the block and I'm robbin' bitches, too
    Up the herringbones and bamboos
    I wouldn't give a fuck if you're tnangerp
    Give me the baby rings and the #1 Mom pendant
    I'm slammin' niggas like Shaquille, shit is real
    When it's time to eat a meal I rob and steal
    'Cause mom duke ain't givin' me shit
    So for the bread and butter, I leave niggas in the gutter
    Huh, word to mother, I'm dangerous
    Crazier than a bag of fuckin' angel dust
    When I bust my gat, motherfuckers take dirt naps
    I'm all that and a dime sack, where the paper at?
    
    
    [Interlude]
    When he's stickin' you and takin' all of your money
    
    [Chorus]
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    (What's mines is mines and what's yours is mine)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    (What's mines is mines and what's yours is mine)
    
    [Verse 2]
    Big up! Big up! It's a stick up! Stick up!
    And I'm shootin' niggas quick if ya hiccup
    Don't let me fill my clip up in ya back and headpiece
    The opposite of peace, sendin' mom duke a wreath
    You're talkin' to the robbery expert
    Step into your wake with your blood on my shirt
    Don't be a jerk and get smoked over bein' resistant
    'Cause when I lick shots them shits is persistent
    Goodness gracious, the papers
    Where the cash at? Where the stash at?
    Nigga, pass that
    Before you get your grave dug from the main thug
    Three fifty-seven slug
    And my nigga Biggie got a itchy one grip
    One in the chamber, thirty-two in the clip
    Motherfuckers better strip, (Yeah, nigga, peel!)
    Before you find out how blue steel feel
    From the Beretta, puttin' all the holes in ya sweater
    The money-getter, motherfuckers know the pedi'
    Rolex watches and colorful Swatches
    I'm diggin' in pockets, motherfuckers can't stop it
    Man, niggas come through, I'm takin' high school rings too
    Bitches get delgnarts for their earrings and bangles
    And when I rock her and drop her, I'm taking her door knockers
    And if she's resistant: blakka, blakka, blakka
    So go get your man, bitch, he can get robbed, too
    Tell him Biggie took it, what the fuck he gonna do?
    Man I hope apologetic or I'm a have to set it
    And if I set it, the cocksucker won't forget it
    
    You might also like
    O Holy Night
    Christmas Songs
    Warning
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    Ready to Die
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    
    [Interlude]
    Hey bitch, hey bitch, gimme your money bitch (When he's stickin' you and takin' all your money)
    
    [Chorus]
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    (What's mines is mines and what's yours is mine)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    Gimme the loot, gimme the loot (I'm a bad, bad, bad)
    (What's mines is mines and what's yours is mine)
    
    [Verse 3]
    Man listen, all this walkin' is hurtin' my feet
    Ooh, money looks sweet
    Where at? In the Isuzu Jeep
    Man, I throw him in the fiend you grab the fucking cream
    And if he start to scream, bom-bom, have a nice dream
    Hold up, he got a fucking bitch in the car
    Fur coats and diamonds, she think she a superstar
    Ooh, Biggie let me jack her, I'll kick her in the back
    Hit her with the gat
    Yo, chill, shorty, let me do that
    Just get the fucking car keys and cruise up the block
    The bitch act shocked getting shot on the spot
    Oh shit, the cops
    Be cool, fool
    They ain't gonna roll up, all they want is fucking doughnuts
    So why the fuck he keep looking?
    I guess to get his life tooken
    I just came home, ain't trying to see Central Booking
    Oh shit, now he looking in my face
    You better haul ass 'cause I ain't with no fucking chase
    So lace up your boots, 'cause I'm about to shoot
    A true motherfucker going out for the loot
    
    
    [Outro]
    Take that motherfuckers
</song>
