<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
[Intro]
Yeah

[Verse 1]
So you wanna be hardcore?
With your hat to the back
Talkin' about the gats in ya raps
But I can't feel that hardcore appeal that you're screamin'
Maybe I'm dreamin'
This ain't Christopher Williams
Still some MC's gotta feel one, caps I gotta peel some
To let niggas know that if you fuck with big-and-heavy
I get up in that ass like a wedgie
Says who? Says me, the lyrical
Niggas sayin', "Biggie off the street, it's a miracle!"
Left the drugs alone, took the thugs along with me
Just for niggas actin' shifty
Sticks and stones break bones, but the gat'll kill ya quicker
Especially when I'm drunk off the liquor
Smokin' funk by the boxes, packin' Glocks-es
It's natural to eat you niggas like chocolates
The funk, baby



[Chorus]
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"

[Verse 2]
All I want is bitches, big-booty bitches
Used to sell crack so I could stack my riches
Now I pack gats to stop all the snitches
From stayin' in my business, what is this?
Relentless approach to know if I'm broke or not
Just 'cause I joke and smoke a lot
Don't mean I don't tote the Glock
Sixteen shots for my niggas in the pen
Until we motherfuckin' meet again, huh
I'm doin' rhymes now, fuck the crimes now
Come on the Ave, I'm real hard to find now
'Cause I'm knee-deep in the beats
In the Land Cruiser Jeep with the MAC-10 by the seats
For the jackers, the jealous-ass crackers in the (blue suits)
I'll make you prove that it's bulletproof
Hold your head 'cause when you hit the bricks
I got gin, mad blunts, and bitches suckin' dick
The funk, baby

You might also like
Gimme the Loot
The Notorious B.I.G.
Things Done Changed
The Notorious B.I.G.
Warning
The Notorious B.I.G.

[Chorus]
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk" (Uh)
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"

[Verse 3]
So I guess you know the story, the rap-side, crack-side
How I smoke funk, smack bitches on the backside
Bed-Stuy, the place where my head rests
Fifty-shot clip if a nigga want test
The rocket launcher, Biggie stomped ya
High as a motherfuckin' helicopter
That's why I pack a Nina, fuck a misdemeanor
Beatin' motherfuckers like Ike beat Tina
"What's love got to do..."
When I'm rippin' all through your whole crew?
Strapped like Bamboo but I don't sling guns
I got bags of funk and it's sellin' by the tons
Niggas wanna know how I live the mack life
Makin' money, smokin' mics like crack pipes
It's type, simple and plain, to maintain
I add a little funk to the brain
The funk, baby


[Chorus]
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
"I live for the funk, I'll die for the funk"
</song>