<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <verse artist = "biggie pop" theme = "none">
        <line>Who the fuck is this, pagin' me at 5:46 in the morning?</line>
        <line>Crack of dawn and now I'm yawnin'</line>
        <line>Wipe the cold out my eye</line>
        <line>See who's this pagin' me and why</line>
        <line>It's my nigga, Pop from the barbershop</line>
        <line>Told me he was in the gambling spot and heard the intricate plot</line>
        <line><style type="simile">Of niggas wanna stick me like flypaper</style>, neighbor</line>
        <line>Slow down, love, please chill, drop the caper</line>
        <line>Remember them niggas from the hill up in Brownsville</line>
        <line>That you rolled dice with, smoked blunts and got nice with?</line>
        <line>Yeah, my nigga Fame up in Prospect</line>
        <line>Nah, them my niggas, nah, love, wouldn't disrespect</line>
        <line>I didn't say them</line>
        <line>They schooled me to some niggas that you knew from back when</line>
        <line>When you was clockin' minor figures</line>
        <line>Now they heard <style type="simile">you're blowin' up like nitro</style></line>
        <line><violence>And they wanna <style type="imagery">stick the knife through your windpipe slow</style></violence></line>
        <line>So, thank Fame for warnin' me, 'cause now I'm warnin' you</line>
        <line>I got the MAC, nigga, tell me what you gonna do</line>
    </verse>
    
    <chorus artist = "biggie" theme = "money">
        <line>Damn, niggas wanna stick me for my paper</line>
        <line>Damn, niggas wanna stick me for my paper</line>
        <line>Damn, niggas wanna stick me for my paper</line>
        <line>Damn, niggas wanna stick me for my paper</line>
    </chorus>
    
    <!-- repetition in the first few lines -->
    <verse artist = "biggie pop" theme = "violence">
        <line><money>They heard about the Rolexes and the Lexus</money></line>
        <line>With the Texas license plates out of state</line>
        <line><money>They heard about the pounds you got down in Georgetown</money></line>
        <line><money>And they heard you got half of Virginia locked down</money></line>
        <line>They even heard about the crib</line>
        <line>You bought your moms out in Florida, the Fifth Corridor</line>
        <line>Call the coroner!</line>
        <line>There's gonna be a lot of slow singin' and flower-bringin'</line>
        <line>If my burglar alarm starts ringin'</line>
        <line>What ya think all the guns is for?</line>
        <line>All-purpose war, got the Rottweilers by the door</line>
        <line>And I feed 'em gunpowder so they can devour</line>
        <line>The criminals tryin' to drop my decimals</line>
        <line>Damn, niggas wanna stick me for my <style type = "collo">cream</style></line>
        <line>And it ain't a dream, things ain't always what it seem</line>
        <line><relationships>It's the ones that smoke blunts with ya, see your picture</relationships></line>
        <line><relationships>Now they wanna grab they guns and come and get ya</relationships></line>
        <line><style type="thirdPerson">Bet ya Biggie won't slip</style></line>
        <line><style type="imagery">I got the Calico with the black talons loaded in the clip</style></line>
        <line>So I can rip through the ligaments</line>
        <line>Put the fuckers in a bad predicament</line>
        <line>Where all the foul niggas went</line>
        <line><style type = "collo">Touch my cheddar, feel my Beretta</style></line>
        <line>Buck what I'ma hit you with, you motherfuckers better duck</line>
        <line><style type="imagery">I bring pain, bloodstains on what remains</style></line>
        <line>Of his jacket, he had a gun, he shoulda packed it</line>
        <line>Cocked it, extra clips in my pocket</line>
        <line>So I can reload and explode on your asshole</line>
        <line>I fuck around and get hardcore</line>
        <line>C-4 to your door, no beef no more, nigga</line>
        <line>Feel the rough, scandalous</line>
        <line>The more weed smoke I puff, the more dangerous</line>
        <line>I don't give a fuck about you or your weak crew</line>
        <line><style type = "thirdPerson">What you gonna do when Big Poppa come for you?</style></line>
        <line>I'm not runnin', nigga, I bust my gun and</line>
        <line>Hold on, I hear somebody comin'</line>
    </verse>
    
    <skit artist = "unknown" theme = "violence">
        <line>C'mon, motherfucker</line>
        <line>Man, I'm comin' as fast as I can</line>
        <line>Just g— bring your motherfuckin' ass on, come on</line>
        <line>Are we gettin' close, huh?</line>
        <line>It's right over here</line>
        <line>You sure it's Biggie Smalls crib, man?</line>
        <line>Yeah, I'm sure, motherfucker, come on</line>
        <line>Man, fuck, this better be his motherfuckin' house</line>
        <line>Fuck, right here</line>
        <line>Tsk, this better be this motherfucker's house</line>
        <line>Oh shit</line>
        <line>What? What's wrong?</line>
        <line>What's that red dot on your head, man?</line>
        <line>What red dot?</line>
        <line>Oh shit! You got a red dot on your head, too</line>
        <line>Oh shit!</line>
    </skit>
</song>
