<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <intro artist = "puffDaddy">
        Yeah, yeah, you ready, motherfucker?
        We gonna kill your ass, kill your ass
        I'm ready
    </intro>
    
    <verse artist = "biggie">
        <theme topic = "lifestyle"><style type = "imagery">As I grab the Glock, put it to your headpiece
        One in the chamber, the safety is off, release
        Straight at your dome, holmes, </style><style type = "metaphor">I wanna see cabbage</style>
        <style type = "thirdPerson">Biggie Smalls the savage</style>, doin' your brain cells much damage
        Teflon is the material for the imperial
        Mic ripper, girl stripper, the Henny sipper
        <style type = "simile">I drop lyrics off and on like a light switch</style>
        Quick to grab the right bitch and make her drive the Q-45
        Glocks and TEC's are expected when I wreck shit
        Respect is collected, so check it!
        <style type = "metaphor">I got techniques drippin' out my butt cheeks
        Sleep on my stomach so I don't fuck up my sheets, huh</style>
        <style type = "simile">My shit is deep, deeper than my grave, G</style>
        I'm ready to die, and nobody can save me
        Fuck the world, fuck my moms and my girl
        My life is played out like a Jheri curl
        I'm ready to die!</theme>
    </verse>
    
    <chorus artist = "biggie">
        Yes, I'm ready
        Yes, I'm ready
        Yes, I'm ready
        So die, motherfuckers, die, motherfuckers, die
    </chorus>
    
    <verse artist = "biggie">
        <theme topic = "wealth">As I sit back and look when I used to be a crook
        Doin' whatever it took, from snatchin' chains to pocketbooks
        A big bad motherfucker on the wrong road
        I got some drugs, tried to get the avenue sold
        I want it all from the Rolexes to the Lexus
        Gettin' paid is all I expected
        My mother didn't give me what I want, what the fuck?!
        Now I've got a Glock makin' motherfuckers duck
        Shit is real and hungry's how I feel
        I rob and steal because that money got that whip appeal</theme>
        Kickin' niggas down the steps just for rep
        Any repercussion lead to niggas gettin' wet
        <style type = "imagery">The infrared's at your head real steady</style>
        You better grab your guns 'cause I'm ready
    </verse>
    
    <chorus artist = "biggie puffDaddy">
        Yes, I'm ready
        Yes, I'm ready
        I'm ready to die
        Yes, I'm ready
        So die motherfuckers, die motherfuckers, die
        Nah, we ain't gonna kill your ass yet, we gonna make you suffer
    </chorus>
    
    <verse artist = "biggie">
        <theme topic = "lifestyle">In a sec, I throw the TEC to your fuckin' neck
        Everybody hit the deck, <style type = "thirdPerson">Biggie 'bout to get some wreck</style>
        Quick to leave you in a coffin for slick talkin'
        <style type = "simile allusion">You better act like CeCe</style>, and keep on walkin'
        <style type = "imagery">When I hit ya, I split ya to the white meat
        You swung a left, you swung a right, you fell to the concrete
        Your face, my feet, they meet with stompin'</style>
        I'm rippin' MC's from Tallahassee to Compton
        <style type = "thirdPerson">Biggie Smalls on a higher plane</style>
        Niggas say I'm strange, deranged because I put the 12 gauge to your brain
        Make your shit splatter
        <style type = "simile">Mix the blood like batter then my pocket gets fatter</style>
        <style type = "imagery">After the hit, leave you on the street with your neck slit
        Down your backbone to where your motherfuckin' shit drip
        The shit I kick rippin' through the vest</style>
        <style type = "thirdPerson">Biggie Smalls passin' any test</style>
        I'm ready to die!</theme>
    </verse>
    
    <chorus artist = "biggie puffDaddy">
        Yes, I'm ready
        Yes, I'm ready
        I'm ready
        Yes, I'm ready
        Time to go, we gon' put you out your misery, motherfucker
        Niggas definitely know what time it is <adlib>Yes, I'm ready</adlib>
        <style type="imagery">The Notorious one</style> in full effect for '93 <adlib>Yes, I'm ready</adlib>
        Uhh, uhh Yes, I'm ready
        Suicidal, I'm ready!
        So die, motherfuckers, die, motherfuckers, die
        Yes, I'm ready
        So die, motherfuckers, die, motherfuckers, die
    </chorus>
    
    <outro artist = "puffDaddy">
        <theme topic="relationship lifestyle">Now I lay me down to sleep <adlib>Yeah</adlib>
        Pray the Lord my soul to keep
        If I should die before I wake
        I pray the Lord my soul to take
        'Cause I'm ready to die
        <adlib>I'm ready, I'm ready</adlib>
        All y'all motherfuckers come with me if you want to
        <adlib>I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready</adlib>
        <style type="thirdPerson">Biggie Smalls the biggest man</style>
        <adlib>I'm Ready</adlib>
        <style type="allusion">Rockin' on and on in '93, Easy Mo Bee
        Third Eye and the rest of the Bad Boy fam</style>
        I don't wanna see no cryin' at my funeral</theme>
    </outro>
</song>
