<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
    <verse artist="Biggie"><theme topic="sex">I used to get feels on a bitch Now I throw shields on
            the dick to stop me from that HIV shit</theme>
        <style type="simile" reference="general">And niggas know they soft like a Twinkie</style> filling Playing the
        villain, prepare for this rap killing Biggie Smalls is the illest,<style> your style is
            played out Like Arnold on that,</style><style type="allusion" reference="TV">"What you talking 'bout,
            Willis?"</style> The thrill is gone, the Black Frank White Is here to excite and throw
        dick to dykes Bitches I like 'em brainless, guns I like 'em stainless steel <style
            type="allusion">I want the fucking fortune like the Wheel</style>
        <theme topic="violence">I squeeze gats 'til my clips is empty</theme> Don't tempt me, you
        don't want to fuck with the M-E...</verse>

    <verse artist="Method Man">...T-H-O-D Man, here I am I'll be damned if this ain't some shit Come
        to spread the butter lyrics over hominy grit It's the low killer death trap, yes I'm a
        jet-black ninja Coming where you rest at, surrender Step inside the ring, you's the number
        one contender Looking cold-booty like your pussy in December Nigga, stop bitching, button up
        your lip and From Method all you getting is a can of ass-whipping Hey, I'll be kicking you
        son, you doing all the yapping Acting as if it can't happen Your frontin' got me mad enough
        to touch something Yo, I'm from Shaolin Island and ain't afraid to bust something So what
        you want nigga? You won't nigga I got a 6-shooter and a horse named Trigger It's real,
            <theme topic="violence">'94 rugged-raw Kickin' down your goddamn door</theme> And it
        goes a little something like this </verse>

    <chorus artist="Method Man Biggie">Fuck the world, don't ask me for shit Everything you get you
        gotta work hard for it <adlib>Honeys shake your hips</adlib> You don't stop <adlib>And
            niggas pack the clips</adlib> Keep on, bitch You might also like Warning The Notorious
        B.I.G. One More Chance The Notorious B.I.G. Fuck Me <adlib>Interlude</adlib> The Notorious
        B.I.G.</chorus>
    <verse artist="Method Man"> Verse two, coming with that Olde E brew Meth-tical, 
        <theme topic="violence"> putting niggas back in ICU</theme>I'm lifted, troop, you can bring
        your wack-ass crew I got connections, <theme topic="violence">I'll get that ass stuck like
            glue</theme> Huh, no question, I be coming down and shit Yo I gets rugged as a
        motherfucking carpet get And niggas love it, not in the physical form but in the mental I
        spark and they cells get warm I'm not a gentleman, I'm a Method Man Baby accept it, utmost
        respect it, and <adlib>Assume the position</adlib> Stop look and listen I spit on your grave
        then I grab my Charles Dickens, bitch</verse>

    <verse artist="Biggie">Welcome to my center, <theme topic="sex">honeys feel it deep in they
            placenta</theme> Cold as the pole in the winter Far from the inventor, but I got this
        rap shit sewed And when my MAC unloads I'm guaranteed another video Ready to die, why I act
        that way? Pop duke left mom duke, the faggot took the back way <theme topic="sex">So instead
            of making hoes suck my dick up</theme> I used to do stick-ups, 'cause hoes is irritating
        like the hiccups Excuse me, flows just grow through me Like trees to branches, cliffs to
        avalanches It's the praying mantis, deep like the mind of Farrakhan A motherfucking rap
        phenomenon, plus <adlib>I got more Glocks and TECs than you</adlib> I make it hot,
            <adlib>niggas won't even stand next to you</adlib>
        <theme topic="violence">Nigga touch me you better bust me three times in the head Or
            motherfucker's dead, you thought so</theme></verse>

    <chorus artist="Biggie">Fuck the world, don't ask me for shit And everything you get you gotta
        work hard for it <adlib>Honeys shake your hips</adlib> You don't stop <adlib>And niggas pack
            the clips</adlib> Keep on, bitch Fuck the world, don't ask me for shit Everything you
        get you gotta work hard for it <adlib>Honeys shake your hips</adlib> You don't stop
            <adlib>And niggas pack the clips</adlib> Keep on, bitch</chorus>

    <outro artist="Method Man Biggie">Junior M.A.F.I.A. clique in full effect <adlib>Yeah, what the
            fuck you want, nigga?</adlib> Ah, yeah, hell yeah <adlib>Biggie Smalls and
            Meth-tical</adlib> Bedford–Stuyvesant the livest one <adlib>9-4 coming at you
            raw</adlib> My borough is thorough <adlib>Shaolin Island, yeah</adlib> Recognize
            <adlib>Yeah</adlib></outro>
</song>
