<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
    [Chorus]
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    
    [Verse 1]
    I know how it feel to wake up fucked up
    Pockets broke as hell, another rock to sell
    People look at you like you's the user
    Sellin' drugs to all the losers, mad buddha abuser
    But they don't know about your stress-filled day
    Baby on the way, mad bills to pay
    That's why you drink Tanqueray, so you can reminisce
    And wish you wasn't livin' so devilish, shit
    I remember I was just like you
    Smokin' blunts with my crew, flippin' over 62's
    'Cause G-E-D wasn't B-I-G
    I got P-A-I-D, that's why my moms hate me
    She was forced to kick me out, no doubt
    Then I figured out nicks went for 20s down South
    Packed up my tools for my raw power move
    Glock 19 for casket and flower moves
    For chumps tryin' to stop my flow
    And what they don't know will show on the autopsy
    Went to see Papi to cop me a brick
    Asked for some consignment, he wasn't tryin' to hear it
    Smokin' mad Newports 'cause I'm due in court
    For an assault that I caught in Bridgeport, New York
    Catch me if you can like the Gingerbread Man
    You better have your gat in hand, 'cause man
    
    
    [Chorus]
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    
    [Verse 2]
    I had the master plan, I'm in the caravan on my way to Maryland
    With my man Two-TECs to take over this projects
    They call him Two-TECs, he tote two TECs
    And when he start to bust, he like to ask, "Who's next?"
    I got my honey on the Amtrak with the crack
    In the crack of her ass, two pounds of hash in the stash
    I wait for hon to make some quick cash
    I told her she could be lieutenant, bitch got gassed
    At last, I'm literally loungin', black
    Sittin' back, countin' double digit thousand stacks
    Had to re-up, see what's up with my peeps
    Toyota deal-athon had it cheap on the Jeeps
    See who got smoked, what rumors was spread
    Last I heard I was dead, with six to the head
    Then I got the phone call, it couldn't hit me harder
    We got infiltrated, like Nino at the Carter
    Heard TEC got murdered in a town I never heard of
    By some bitch named Alberta over nickel-plated burners
    And my bitch swear to God she won't snitch
    I told her when she hit the bricks I'll make the hooker rich
    Conspiracy, she'll be home in three
    Until then I looks out for the whole family
    A true G, that's me, blowin' like a bubble
    In the everyday struggle
    
    You might also like
    Suicidal Thoughts
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    The What
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    One More Chance
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    
    [Chorus]
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    
    [Verse 3]
    I'm seein' body after body and our mayor Giuliani
    Ain't tryin' to see no black man turn to John Gotti
    My daughter use a potty so she's older now
    Educated street knowledge, I'ma mold her now
    Trick a little dough buyin' young girls fringes
    Dealin' with the dope fiend binges, seein' syringes
    In the veins, hard to explain how I maintain
    The crack smoke make my brain feel so strange
    Breakin' days on the set, no sweat
    Drunk off Moët, can't bag yet because it's still wet
    But when that dry, baggin' five at a time
    I can clock about nine on the check cashin' line
    I had the first and the third, rehearse, that's my word
    Thick in the game, D's knew my first name
    Should I quit? Shit no, even though they had me scared
    Yo, they got a eight, I got a TEC with air holes
    
    
    [Interlude: The Notorious B.I.G. & Puff Daddy]
    And that's just how the shit go in the struggle, motherfucker
    Hah, come on, what you say?
    
    [Chorus]
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    I don't wanna live no more
    Sometimes I hear death knockin' at my front door
    I'm livin' every day like a hustle, another drug to juggle
    Another day, another struggle (Right)
    
    [Outro: The Notorious B.I.G. & Puff Daddy]
    Junior M.A.F.I.A. right
    Yeah, rock on, woo!
    Biggie Smalls, right
    Junior M.A.F.I.A
</song>
