<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>

    <intro artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">
        <line>Uh, uh, check it out <adlib>Yeah</adlib>, uh </line>
        <line>Junior M.A.F.I.A., uh <adlib>He-he</adlib></line>
        <line>Uh <adlib>I like this</adlib> yeah, yeah</line>
        <line>Nine-fo' <adlib>Keep bangin'</adlib></line>
    </intro>


    <verse artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">
        <line>To all the ladies in the place with style and grace</line>
        <line>Allow me to lace these lyrical douches in your bushes <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
        <line>Who rock grooves and make moves with all the mamis?</line> 
        <line><theme topic="drugs">The back of the club, sippin' Moët is where you'll find me</theme><adlib>What?</adlib></line>
        <line>The back of the club, <style type="collo">mackin' hoes</style>, my crew's behind me <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
        <line><style type="collo">Mad question askin'</style>, <theme topic="drugs">blunt passin'</theme></line>
        <line>Music blastin', but I just can't quit</line>
        <line>Because one of these honeys Biggie got to creep with <adlib>That's right</adlib></line>
        <line>Sleep with, keep the ep a secret, why not? <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
        <line>Why blow up my spot 'cause we both got hot?</line>
        <line>Now check it: I got more mack than Craig, and in the bed</line>
        <line>Believe me, sweetie, I got enough to feed the needy <adlib>Come on</adlib></line>
        <line>No need to be greedy, I got mad friends with Benzes</line> 
        <line><theme topic="money">C-notes by the layers</theme>, true fuckin' players <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
        <line>Jump in the Rover and come over, tell your friends jump in the GS3</line>
        <line>I got the chronic by the tree cuz <adlib>Let's go</adlib></line>
    </verse>

    <chorus artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>Throw your hands in the air if you's a true player</line>
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>To the honeys gettin' money, playin' niggas like dummies</line>
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>You got a gun up in your waist, please don't shoot up the place <adlib>Why?</adlib></line>
        <line>'Cause I see some ladies tonight that should be havin' my baby <adlib>Uh</adlib>, baby <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
    </chorus>

    <verse artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">
        <line>Straight up, honey, really I'm askin'</line>
        <line><style type="collo">Most of these niggas think they be mackin'</style>, but they be actin'</line>
        <line>Who they attractin' with that line <adlib>What?</adlib>,"What's your name? What's your sign?"</line>
        <line>Soon as he buy that wine, I just creep up from behind <adlib>That's right</adlib></line>
        <line>And ask you what your interests are, who you be with</line>
        <line>Things that make you smile, what numbers to dial</line>
        <line>You gon' be here for a while? I'm gon' go call my crew, you go call your crew</line>
        <line>We can rendezvous at the bar around 2 <adlib>Come on</adlib></line>
        <line>Plans to leave, throw the keys to Little Cease <adlib>Uh-huh</adlib></line>
        <line>Pull the truck up front, and <theme topic="drugs">roll up the next blunt</theme></line>
        <line><theme topic="drugs">So we can <style type="collo">steam on the way to the telly</style></theme>, go fill my belly <adlib>G</adlib></line>
        <line>A T-bone steak, cheese eggs and Welch's grape</line>
        <line>Conversate for a few, ‘cause in a few we gon' do</line>
        <line>What we came to do, ain't that right, boo? <adlib>True</adlib></line>
        <line>Forget the telly—we just go to the crib</line>
        <line>And watch a movie in the jacuzzi, <theme topic="drugs sex"><style type="collo">smoke Ls</style> while you do me</theme></line>
    </verse>

    <chorus artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>Throw your hands in the air if you's a true player <adlib>Come on, yeah</adlib></line>
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>To the honeys gettin' money, playin' niggas like dummies <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>You got a gun up in your waist, please don't shoot up the place <adlib>Why?</adlib></line>
        <line>'Cause I see some ladies tonight that should be havin' my baby, baby <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
    </chorus>

    <verse artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">
        <line><adlib>How you livin', Biggie Smalls?</adlib> In mansion and Benzes</line>
        <line>Givin' ends to my friends, and it feels stupendous</line>
        <line>Tremendous cream: fuck a dollar and a dream <adlib>Heh</adlib></line>
        <line>Still tote gats, strapped with infrared beams <adlib>That's right</adlib> <adlib>What?</adlib></line>
        <line>Choppin' Os <adlib>Uh-huh</adlib>, smokin' la in Optimos</line>
        <line>Money, hoes and clothes: all a nigga knows <adlib>All a nigga knows</adlib></line>
        <line>A foolish pleasure? Whatever</line>
        <line>I had to find the buried treasure<adlib>For what?</adlib>, so grams I had to measure</line>
        <line>However, livin' better now, Coogi sweater now</line>
        <line>Drop top BMs, I'm the man, girlfriend</line>
    </verse>

    <interlude artist="PuffDaddy">
        <line>Yeah, honey, check it</line>
        <line>Tell your friends to get with my friends</line>
        <line>And we can be friends</line>
        <line>Shit, we can do this every weekend <adlib>That's right</adlib>, alright?</line>
        <line>Is that aight wit' you?</line>
        <line>Yeah, keep bangin'</line>
    </interlude>

    <chorus artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>Throw your hands in the air if you's a true player</line>
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>To the honeys gettin' money, playin' niggas like dummies <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
        <line>I love it when you call me Big Poppa</line>
        <line>You got a gun up in your waist, please don't shoot up the place <adlib>Why?</adlib></line>
        <line>'Cause I see some ladies tonight that should be havin' my baby, baby <adlib>Uh</adlib></line>
    </chorus>

    <outro artist="Biggie">
        <line>Check it out</line>
        <line>Nine-fo' shit for that ass, uh</line>
        <line>Puff Daddy, Biggie Smalls, Junior M.A.F.I.A.</line>
        <line>Represent, baby, baby, uh</line>
    </outro>
</song>
