<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>

    <intro artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">Uh, uh, check it out <adlib>Yeah</adlib>, uh Junior M.A.F.I.A.,
        uh <adlib>He-he</adlib> Uh <adlib>I like this</adlib> yeah, yeah Nine-fo' <adlib>Keep
            bangin'</adlib></intro>


    <verse artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">To all the ladies in the place with style and grace Allow me to
        lace these lyrical douches in your bushes <adlib>Uh</adlib> Who rock grooves and make moves
        with all the mamis? <theme topic="drugs">The back of the club, sippin' Moët is where you'll
            find me</theme>
        <adlib>What?</adlib> The back of the club, mackin' hoes, my crew's behind me
            <adlib>Uh</adlib>
        <style type="collo">Mad question askin'</style>, blunt passin' Music blastin', but I just
        can't quit Because one of these honeys Biggie got to creep with <adlib>That's right</adlib>
        Sleep with, keep the ep a secret, why not? <adlib>Uh</adlib> Why blow up my spot 'cause we
        both got hot? Now check it: I got more mack than Craig, and in the bed Believe me, sweetie,
        I got enough to feed the needy <adlib>Come on</adlib>
        <theme topic="money">No need to be greedy, I got mad friends with Benzes C-notes by the
            layers, true fuckin' players</theme>
        <adlib>Uh</adlib> Jump in the Rover and come over, tell your friends jump in the GS3 I got
        the chronic by the tree cuz <adlib>Let's go</adlib></verse>



    <chorus artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">I love it when you call me Big Poppa Throw your hands in the
        air if you's a true player I love it when you call me Big Poppa To the honeys gettin' money,
        playin' niggas like dummies I love it when you call me Big Poppa You got a gun up in your
        waist, please don't shoot up the place <adlib>Why?</adlib> 'Cause I see some ladies tonight
        that should be havin' my baby <adlib>Uh), baby (Uh</adlib></chorus>


    <verse artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">Straight up, honey, really I'm askin' Most of these niggas
        think they be mackin', but they be actin' Who they attractin' with that line
            <adlib>What?</adlib>, "What's your name? What's your sign?" Soon as he buy that wine, I
        just creep up from behind <adlib>That's right</adlib> And ask you what your interests are,
        who you be with Things that make you smile, what numbers to dial You gon' be here for a
        while? I'm gon' go call my crew, you go call your crew We can rendezvous at the bar around 2
            <adlib>Come on</adlib> Plans to leave, throw the keys to Little Cease
            <adlib>Uh-huh</adlib> Pull the truck up front, and <theme topic="drugs">roll up the next
            blunt</theme> So we can steam on the way to the telly, go fill my belly <adlib>G</adlib>
        A T-bone steak, cheese eggs and Welch's grape Conversate for a few, ‘cause in a few we gon'
        do What we came to do, ain't that right, boo? <adlib>True</adlib> Forget the telly—we just
        go to the crib And watch a movie in the jacuzzi, <theme topic="drugs sex">smoke Ls while you
            do me</theme></verse>


    <chorus artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">I love it when you call me Big Poppa Throw your hands in the
        air if you's a true player <adlib>Come on, yeah</adlib> I love it when you call me Big Poppa
        To the honeys gettin' money, playin' niggas like dummies <adlib>Uh</adlib> I love it when
        you call me Big Poppa You got a gun up in your waist, please don't shoot up the place
            <adlib>Why?</adlib> 'Cause I see some ladies tonight that should be havin' my baby, baby
            <adlib>Uh</adlib></chorus>


    <verse artist="Biggie PuffDaddy"><adlib>How you livin', Biggie Smalls?</adlib> In mansion and
        Benzes Givin' ends to my friends, and it feels stupendous Tremendous cream: fuck a dollar
        and a dream <adlib>Heh</adlib> Still tote gats, strapped with infrared beams <adlib>That's
            right) (What?</adlib> Choppin' Os <adlib>Uh-huh</adlib>, smokin' la in Optimos Money,
        hoes and clothes: all a nigga knows <adlib>All a nigga knows</adlib> A foolish pleasure?
        Whatever I had to find the buried treasure <adlib>For what?</adlib>, so grams I had to
        measure However, livin' better now, Coogi sweater now Drop top BMs, I'm the man,
        girlfriend</verse>


    <interlude artist="PuffDaddy">Yeah, honey, check it Tell your friends to get with my friends And
        we can be friends Shit, we can do this every weekend <adlib>That's right</adlib>, alright?
        Is that aight wit' you? Yeah, keep bangin'</interlude>



    <chorus artist="Biggie PuffDaddy">I love it when you call me Big Poppa Throw your hands in the
        air if you's a true player I love it when you call me Big Poppa To the honeys gettin' money,
        playin' niggas like dummies <adlib>Uh</adlib> I love it when you call me Big Poppa You got a
        gun up in your waist, please don't shoot up the place <adlib>Why?</adlib> 'Cause I see some
        ladies tonight that should be havin' my baby, baby <adlib>Uh</adlib></chorus>


    <outro artist="Biggie">Check it out Nine-fo' shit for that ass, uh Puff Daddy, Biggie Smalls,
        Junior M.A.F.I.A. Represent, baby, baby, uh</outro>
</song>
