<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    
    <intro artist="Biggie DianaKing">
        <line>No big up our gun men, seen? <adlib>Big up, big up</adlib></line>
        <line>Cuh dis ah '94 when ah RAA fi kill people and kyaan dun</line>
        <line>Nuh waan pussy hole hold di kaanah</line>
        <line>Watch this, lawd</line>
    </intro>
    
    <chorus artist="DianaKing">
        <line>Me holla respect, to all the gun men dem</line>
        <line>Gun men alone, keep gun men friend</line>
        <line>Fire bun, fi all the informer dem</line>
        <line>Informer lone keep informer friend</line>
    </chorus>   
    
    <verse artist="Biggie">
        <line>1970 something, nigga I don't sweat the date</line>
        <line><theme topic="family">My moms is late so I had to plan my escape</theme></line>
        <line>Out the skins, in this world of fly girls</line>
        <line><theme topic="drugs">Tanqueray and Hennessy until I call hurl</theme></line>
        <line>Ten months in this gut, what the fuck?</line>
        <line>I wish moms would hurry up so I could get buck</line>
        <line>Wild juvenile ripping mics and shit</line>
        <line>New York, New York, ready for the likes of this</line>
        <line>Then came the worst date, May 21st</line>
        <line>2:19, that's when my mama water burst</line>
        <line>No spouse in the house so she rode for self</line>
        <line>To the hospital, to see if she could get a little help</line>
        <line>Umbilical cord's wrapped around my neck</line>
        <line>I'm seeing my death and I ain't even took my first step</line>
        <line>I made it out, I'm bringing mad joy</line>
        <line>The doctor looked and said, "He's going to be a bad boy"</line>
    </verse>
      
    <chorus artist="DianaKing">
        <line>Me holla respect, to all the gun men dem</line>
        <line>Gun men alone, keep gun men friend</line>
        <line>Fire bun, fi all the informer dem</line>
        <line>Informer lone keep informer friend</line>
    </chorus>   
    
    <verse artist="Biggie">
        <line>Now I'm thirteen, <theme topic="drugs">smoking blunts</theme>, making cream</line>
        <line><theme topic="drugs">On the drug scene, fuck a football team</theme></line>
        <line>Risking ruptured spleens by the age of sixteen</line>
        <line>Hearing the coach scream ain't my lifetime dream</line>
        <line>I mean, <theme topic="money">I want to blow up, <style type="collo">stack my dough up</style></theme></line>
        <line>So school I didn't show up, it fucked my flow up</line>
        <line><theme topic="family">Mom said that I should grow up and check myself</theme></line>
        <line>Before I wreck myself, disrespect myself</line>
        <line>Put the drugs on the shelf? Nah, couldn't see it</line>
        <line><style type="allusion">Scarface, King of New York,</style> I want to be it</line>
        <line><theme topic="reflection money">Rap was secondary, money was necessary</theme></line>
        <line>Until I got incarcerated, kinda scary</line>
        <line>C74-Mark 8 set me straight</line>
        <line>Not able to move behind the great steel gate</line>
        <line>Time to contemplate, damn, where did I fail?</line>
        <line>All the money I stacked was all the money for bail</line>
    </verse>
     
    <chorus artist="DianaKing">
        <line>Me holla respect, to all the gun men dem</line>
        <line>Gun men alone, keep gun men friend</line>
        <line>Fire bun, fi all the informer dem</line>
        <line>Informer lone keep informer friend</line>
        <line>Me holla respect, to all the gun men dem</line>
        <line>Gun men alone, keep gun men friend</line>
        <line>Fire bun, fi all the informer dem</line>
        <line>Informer lone keep informer friend</line>
    </chorus>
      
    <verse artist="Biggie">
        <line>Ninety-four, now I explore new horizons</line>
        <line><theme topic="family">Mama smile when she see me, that's surprising</theme></line>
        <line>Honeys is tantalizing, they freak all night</line>
        <line>Keep ducking cops on the creep all night</line>
        <line>As I open my eyes and realizing I changed</line>
        <line>Not the same deranged child stuck up in the game</line>
        <line>And to my niggas living street life</line>
        <line>Learn to treat life to the best, put stress to rest</line>
        <line>Still tote your vest man, niggas be tripping</line>
        <line><style type="collo">In the streets without a gat?</style> Nah, nigga you're slipping</line>
        <line>If I'm dipping on The F with weed on my breath</line>
        <line>Original hustler with the muffler on the TEC</line>
        <line>Respect to the macks in the Ac's</line>
        <line>To the freaks in the Jeeps, lick shots to my peeps</line>
    </verse>
    
    <chorus artist="DianaKing">
        <line>Me holla respect, to all the gun men dem</line>
        <line>Gun men alone, keep gun men friend</line>
        <line>Fire bun, fi all the informer dem</line>
        <line>Informer lone keep informer friend</line>
    </chorus>
      
    <verse artist="DianaKing">
        <line>Now this is Diana King doing a Yankee thing</line>
        <line>In a Biggie Small's thing, do it, Ja</line>
        <line>Have mercy!</line>
        <line>The gunman in all de party</line>
        <line>And everybody feel irie</line>
        <line>And everybody just follow me, follow me, follow me</line>
        <line>Have mercy</line>
        <line>The wul ah we in ah de party</line>
        <line>And everybody look irie</line>
        <line>Now di man them sexy, sexy, sexy</line>
        <line>Do it</line>
    </verse>
     
    <outro artist="DianaKing">
        <line>No mercy fuh nuh big up unnu self</line>
        <line>Cuh we nuh watch nuh this girl seen?</line>
        <line>The hardcore thing we ah deal with</line>
        <line>Oh yes, we are the best</line>
        <line>No other guy can test</line>
    </outro>
       
    <skit artist="Biggie FaithEvans">
        <line>Shit, Mami, damn, why you actin like that, man?</line>
        <line>'Cause I don't be doin' this</line>
        <line>I'm sayin', you know it ain't nothin'</line>
        <line>It's just part of sex, ya know'm saying</line>
        <line>But you know I don't do this</line>
        <line>I don't even know how to do this</line>
        <line>I'm just sayin', jus— just a little peck Mami, for daddy</line>
        <line>Just a little peck</line>
        <line>Like that?</line>
        <line>That's what I'm sayin', yeah</line>
        <line>You know I don't be doin' this though</line>
        <line>You know that</line>
        <line>Whatever bitch!</line>
    </skit>
</song>
