<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
    [Intro: The Notorious B.I.G.]
    No, fuck the bitches, fuck all the stank-ass hoes
    All my niggas know
    Junior M.A.F.I.A. clique, Gucci Don, you know how we play
    Fuckin' scandalous-ass bitches
    You know how it go, Gooch
    I meet a bitch, fuck a bitch
    Next thing you know, you fuckin' a bitch
    You just pass around shit, pass the shit like a cold and shit
    Fuck 'em
    
    
    [Verse 1: The Notorious B.I.G. & Lil' Kim]
    Now when I'm fucking off gin I'm invincible
    Don't love no ho, that's my principle
    'Cause, uh, bitches come (And uh) bitches go (Uh)
    That's why I get my nut and I be out the fucking door (You know)
    They might be the one to set me up
    Want to get they little brother to wet me up
    That's why I tote TECs and stuff, to get them off my case
    Just in case the little fucker ends up misplaced
    I don't give a bitch enough to catch the bus
    And when I see the semen I'm leaving
    Bitches be scheming, I kid you not
    That's why I keep my windows locked and my Glock cocked
    One ho said, Big, why you so hard on us?
    Why you swear all bitches are so scandalous?
    Thug nigga 'til the end, tell a friend, bitch
    'Cause when I like you, then you go and fuck my friend, bitch
    And you know that ain't right
    
    [Chorus]
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    
    [Verse 2: The Notorious B.I.G. & Lil' Kim]
    You see, I don't sweat these hoes
    I keep them in flavors like Timbos and Girbauds
    Bitches just like to play the merry-go
    Yeah we know, drop the scenario
    It was me, Dee, the MPV
    The blunts and brew thang, knocking some Wu-tang
    M-E-T-H-Oh shit, look at them lips and them hips on that bitch
    Dee hit the dip, so I can drop my mackadocious shit
    Light the blunt clip and recognize a pimp
    Needless to speak, the G's obsolete
    Don't sleep, banged the skins in a week
    On the creep up the avenue
    I seen her on the block, who she rapping to?
    That's my nigga Dee, damn he got G
    Now she fucking him and fucking me, see
    You know that ain't right
    
    You might also like
    Suicidal Thoughts
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    Unbelievable
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    Things Done Changed
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    
    [Chorus]
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine, uh
    
    [Verse 3: The Notorious B.I.G.]
    Now I play her far like a moon play a star
    She still sweat me hard 'cause I'm a rap star
    I be cruising up the block, I be passing her
    Pimping hard with a female passenger
    And the only time I call her to hang
    Is when me and Dee blunted up, pissy, scheming on a gangbang
    She should have used her intuition
    Then she wouldn't be classified in that position, listen
    She's saying I dissed her 'cause I'm fucking her sister
    A message to the fellas, that really gets 'em pissed, uh
    But she started that fucking family
    She fucked my man Dee, so why she mad at me? (True)
    Plus your sister look better than you
    Give head better than you, pussy get wetter than you
    So break the fuck out like a rash
    I'm glad I ain't spend no cash to hit your nasty ass
    
    [Chorus]
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
    You know that ain't right with a friend of mine
</song>
