<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>


<song>
  <intro artist="Biggie">
    <style type="repetition">Biggie Smalls is the illest <adlib>Uh</adlib> What? Uh Biggie— Biggie—
      Biggie Smalls is the illest Uh Biggie Smalls, Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls Biggie— Biggie—
      Biggie Smalls is the illest Uh, yeah Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the
    illest</style></intro>
  <verse artist="Biggie">
    <theme topic="home">Live from Bedford-Stuyvesant</theme>, the livest one <theme topic="home"
      >Representing BK to the fullest</theme> Gats, I pull it Bastards ducking when B.I.G. be
    bucking Chickenheads be clucking, in my back room fucking It ain't nothing They know B.I.G. be
    handling With the MAC in the Ac' door paneling Bandaging MC's, oxygen, they can't breathe Mad
    tricks up the sleeve Wear boxers so my dick can breathe Breeze through in the Q Forty-five by my
    side, lyrical high And those that rushes my clutches get put on crutches <theme topic="violence"
      > Get smoked like Dutches from the master Hate to blast ya but I have to</theme>
    <theme topic="violence">You see I smoke a lot</theme>
    <style type="allusion">Your life is played out like Kwame</style> And them fucking polka dots
    Who rock the spot? Biggie <theme topic="drugs"> You know how the weed go, unbelievable</theme>
  </verse>
  <chorus artist="Biggie">
    <style type="repetition">It's unbelievable Biggie Smalls is the illest It's unbelievable Biggie—
      Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest It's unbelievable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the
      illest It's unbelievable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest</style></chorus>
  <verse artist="Biggie"> B-I-G, G-I-E A-K-A., B-I-G Get it? Biggie Also known as the bon appétit
    Rappers can't sleep need sleeping B.I.G. keep creeping <theme topic="violence"> Bullets
      heat-seeking, casualties need treating</theme> Dumb rappers need teaching Lesson A: Don't fuck
    with B-I That's that "Oh I, thought he was wack" Oh, come, come now, why y'all so dumb now Hunt
    me or be hunted I got three hundred and fifty-seven ways To simmer sauté, I'm the winner all day
    Lights get dimmer down Biggie's hallway My forte causes Caucasians to say "He sounds demented"
      <theme topic="drugs"> Car weed scented, if I said it, I meant it</theme> Bite my tongue for no
    one Call me evil, or unbelievable </verse>
  <chorus artist="Biggie">
    <style type="repetition">It's unbelievable Biggie Smalls is the illest It's unbelievable Biggie—
      Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest It's unbelievable Biggie Smalls is the illest It's
      unbelievable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest</style>
  </chorus>
  <verse artist="Biggie">
    <theme topic="violence"> Buck shots out the sun roof of Lexus coupes Leave no witnesses, what
      you think this is? Ain't no amateurs here</theme> I damage and tear, MC's fear me They too
    near not to hear me Clearly, I'm the triple beam dream One thousand grams of uncut to the gut It
    seems fucked up, the way I touched up the grill Trying to play gorilla when you ain't no killer
    The gat's by your liver, your upper lip quiver <theme topic="death">Get ready to die, tell God I
      said hi</theme> And throw down some ice for the nicest MC Niggas know the steelo,
    unbelievable</verse>
  <chorus artist="Biggie">
    <style type="repetition">It's unbelievable Biggie Smalls is the illest It's unbelievable Biggie—
      Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest It's unbelievable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the
      illest It's unbelievable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest</style>
  </chorus>
  <outro artist="Biggie">
    <style type="repetition">It's unbelievable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest
      'Believable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls is the illest 'Believable Biggie— Biggie— Biggie
      Smalls is the illest Biggie Smalls— Biggie— Biggie— Biggie Smalls Biggie— Biggie— Biggie
      Smalls is the illest</style>
  </outro>
</song>
