<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<song>

  <intro artist="Puff Daddy"> Hello? Aw shit, nigga! The fuck time is it, man? Oh, God damn Nigga,
    do you know what time it is? Aw shit, what the fuck's goin' on? You aight? Ah, nigga, what the
    fuck is wrong with you?</intro>


  <verse artist="Biggie  Puff Daddy">
    <style type="reflection">When I die, fuck it, I wanna go to hell 'Cause I'm a piece of shit, it
      ain't hard to fuckin' tell </style><adlib>What you talkin' 'bout, man?</adlib> It don't make
    sense, goin' to heaven with the goodie-goodies Dressed in white, I like black Timbs and black
    hoodies <adlib>Aw, man</adlib> God'll probably have me on some real strict shit No sleepin' all
    day, <theme topic="sex">no gettin' my dick licked</theme> Hangin' with the goodie-goodies,
    loungin' in paradise <theme topic="violence"> Fuck that shit, I wanna tote guns and shoot
      dice</theme>
    <adlib>You talkin' some crazy shit now, nigga</adlib> All my life I been considered as the worst
    Lyin' to my mother, even stealin' out her purse <adlib>Ah</adlib> Crime after crime, from drugs
    to extortion <theme topic="reflection">
      <theme topic="family">I know my mother wish she got a fuckin' abortion She don't even love me
        like she did when I was younger <adlib>Yo, get a hold of yourself, nigga</adlib> Suckin' on
        her chest just to stop my fuckin' hunger I wonder; if I died, would tears come to her eyes?
        Forgive me for my disrespect, forgive me for my lies <adlib>You're buggin',
        B</adlib></theme>
      <theme topic="family">My baby mother's eight months, her little sister's two</theme> Who's to
      blame for both of them? <adlib>Nah, nigga, not you</adlib> I swear to God I want to just slit
      my wrists and end this bullshit Throw the Magnum to my head, threaten to pull shit
        <adlib>Nigga, what the fuck?</adlib> And squeeze until the bed's completely red <adlib>It's
        too late for this shit, man</adlib> I'm glad I'm dead, a worthless fuckin' buddha head The
      stress is buildin' up, I can't— I can't believe <adlib>Ayo, I'm on my way over there,
        man</adlib>
      <theme topic="death"> Suicide's on my fuckin' mind, I wanna leave I swear to God I feel like
        death is fuckin' callin' me</theme> But nah, you wouldn't understand Nigga, talk to me
      please, man! You see, <style type="allusion">it's kinda like the crack did to Pookie in New
        Jack</style> Except when I cross over, there ain't no comin' back <adlib>Ayo, ayo, man, I'm
        out</adlib> Should I die on the train track like <style type="allusion">Ramo in Beat Street?
        </style><adlib>I'ma call you when I get in the car</adlib> People at the funeral frontin'
      like they miss me <adlib>Ayo, where your girl at, man?</adlib> My baby mama kiss me, but she
      glad I'm gone <adlib>Yo, put your girl on the phone, nigga!</adlib> She know me and her sister
      had somethin' goin' on I reach my peak, I can't speak <adlib>Ayo, you listenin' to me,
        motherfucker?</adlib> Call my nigga Chic, tell him that my will is weak <adlib>Ayo, c'mon,
        nigga</adlib> I'm sick of niggas lyin' <adlib>Cut that, I'm sick of bitches hawkin'
        Ayo</adlib> Matter of fact, I'm sick of talkin' <adlib>Nigga, yo, yo, Big! Ayo,
        chill!</adlib>
      <style type="onomatopeia">*Gunshot*</style> Ayo, Big! Ayo, Big!</theme>
  </verse>


  <outro artist="Biggie">
    <style type="repetition">Please hang up and try your call again Please hang up</style>— Is a
    recording</outro>
</song>
