<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
    [Intro: Puffy & The Notorious B.I.G.]
    As we proceed to give you what you need (Uh)
    9-5, motherfuckers
    Get live, motherfuckers
    As we proceed to give you what you need
    9-5, motherfuckers
    Get live, motherfuckers (Now turn the mics up)
    As we proceed to give you what you need (Turn that mic up)
    (Yeah, that beat is knocking, I need that mic up, though)
    (Turn that shit the fuck up)
    East Coast, motherfuckers (Uh, what?)
    Bad Boy, motherfuckers (Turn it up louder, yeah, uh)
    As we proceed to give you what you need
    J.M., motherfuckers
    J.M., motherfuckers (Uh)
    9-5, motherfuckers (Uh)
    
    
    [Verse 1: The Notorious B.I.G.]
    Who shot ya? Separate the weak from the obsolete
    Hard to creep them Brooklyn streets
    It's on, nigga, fuck all that bickerin' beef
    I can hear sweat tricklin' down your cheek
    Your heartbeat sound like Sasquatch feet
    Thunderin', shakin' the concrete
    Then the shit stop when I foil the plot
    Neighbors call the cops, said they heard mad shots
    Saw me in the drop, three and a quarter
    Slaughter, electrical tape around your daughter
    Old school, new school need to learn though
    I burn, baby, burn, like "Disco Inferno"
    Burn slow like blunts with yayo
    Peel more skins than Idaho Potato
    Niggas know; the lyrical molesting is taking place
    Fucking with B.I.G., it ain't safe
    I make your skin chafe, rashes on them asses
    Bumps and bruises, blunts and Land Cruisers
    Big Poppa smash fools, bash fools
    Niggas mad because I know that cash rules
    Everything around me, two Glock nines
    Any motherfucker whispering about mines (And I'm)
    And I'm Crooklyn's finest (Crooklyn's finest)
    You rewind this, Bad Boy's behind this (Bad Boy's behind this)
    
    You might also like
    Hit ’Em Up
    2Pac
    Suicidal Thoughts
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    Juicy
    The Notorious B.I.G.
    
    [Interlude: Puffy & The Notorious B.I.G.]
    As we proceed to give you what you need (What?)
    9-5, motherfuckers (What?)
    Get live, motherfuckers
    As we proceed to give you what you need (What?)
    East Coast, motherfuckers
    Bad Boy, motherfuckers
    Get high, motherfuckers
    Get high, motherfuckers (Uh, uh)
    Smoke blunts, motherfuckers (Uh)
    Get high, motherfuckers (9-5, uh)
    Ready to die, motherfuckers (Uh)
    9-5, motherfuckers (Uh)
    
    [Verse 2: The Notorious B.I.G.]
    I seen the light excite all the freaks
    Stack mad chips, spread love with my peeps
    Niggas wanna creep, gotta watch my back
    Think the Cognac and indo sack make me slack?
    I switches all that, cocksucker, G's up
    One false move, get Swiss cheesed up
    Clip to TEC, respect, I demand it
    Slip and break the 11th Commandment
    Thou shalt not fuck with nor see Poppa
    Feel a thousand deaths when I drop you
    I feel for you, like Chaka Khan, I'm the don
    Pussy when I want, Rolex on the arm
    You'll die slow but calm
    Recognize my face so there won't be no mistake
    So you know where to tell Jake, lame nigga
    Brave nigga, turned front page nigga
    Puff Daddy flips daily
    I smoke the blunts he sips on the Baileys
    On the rocks, tote Glocks at christenings
    Hammer cock, in the fire position and—
    
    
    [Interlude: The Notorious B.I.G.]
    Come here, come here (It ain't gotta be like that, B.I.G.)
    Open your fucking mouth, open your—
    Didn't I tell you don't fuck with me? (Come on, man) Huh?
    Didn't I tell you not to fuck with me? (Come on, man) Huh?
    (Come on, man) Look at you now, huh? (Come on, man)
    Can't talk with a gun in your mouth, huh?
    Bitch-ass nigga, what?
    Who shot ya?
    
    [Outro: Puffy & The Notorious B.I.G.]
    To give you what you need
    9-5, motherfuckers
    Get live, motherfuckers
    Get high, motherfuckers (Who shot ya?)
    Ready to die, motherfuckers, hah!
    As we proceed (Who shot ya?)
    To give you what you need
    9-5, motherfuckers
    East Coast, motherfucker (Who shot ya?)
    West Coast, motherfuckers (Uh)
    West Coast, motherfuckers, hah!
    As we proceed to give you what you need
    As we proceed to give you what you need (As we proceed to give you what you need)
    Get live, motherfuckers
    Get live, motherfuckers (Get live, motherfuckers)
    9-5, motherfuckers (9-5, motherfuckers)
    Get money, motherfuckers
    As we proceed to give you what you need (As we proceed to give you what you need)
    Get live, motherfuckers (Get live, motherfuckers)
    9-5, motherfuckers
    J.M., motherfuckers
    J.M., motherfuckers
    As we proceed
    To give you what you need
    9-5
</song>
