<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song>
 <?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
 
  <intro artist="Puffy  Biggie">As we proceed to give you what you need <adlib>Uh</adlib>
    <style type="repetition">9-5, motherfuckers</style> Get live, motherfuckers As we proceed to
    give you what you need <style type="repetition"> 9-5, motherfuckers</style> Get live,
    motherfuckers <adlib>Now turn the mics up</adlib> As we proceed to give you what you need
      <adlib>Turn that mic up</adlib>
    <adlib>Yeah, that beat is knocking, I need that mic up, though</adlib>
    <adlib>Turn that shit the fuck up</adlib> East Coast, motherfuckers <adlib>Uh, what?</adlib> Bad
    Boy, motherfuckers <adlib>Turn it up louder, yeah, uh</adlib> As we proceed to give you what you
    need <style type="repetition">J.M., motherfuckers J.M., motherfuckers <adlib>Uh</adlib> 9-5,
      motherfuckers <adlib>Uh</adlib></style></intro>



  <verse artist="Biggie"> Who shot ya? Separate the weak from the obsolete Hard to creep them <theme
      topic="home">Brooklyn streets</theme> It's on, nigga, fuck all that bickerin' beef I can hear
    sweat tricklin' down your cheek Your heartbeat sound like Sasquatch feet Thunderin', shakin' the
    concrete Then the shit stop when I foil the plot <theme topic="violence">Neighbors call the
      cops, said they heard mad shots Saw me in the drop, three and a quarter Slaughter, electrical
      tape around your daughter</theme> Old school, new school need to learn though <style
      type="allusion">I burn, baby, burn, like "Disco Inferno"</style> Burn slow like blunts with
    yayo Peel more skins than Idaho Potato Niggas know; the lyrical molesting is taking place <theme
      topic="violence">Fucking with B.I.G., it ain't safe I make your skin chafe, rashes on them
      asses Bumps and bruises, blunts and Land Cruisers Big Poppa smash fools, bash fools <theme
        topic="money">Niggas mad because I know that cash rules</theme> Everything around me, two
      Glock nines</theme> Any motherfucker whispering about mines <adlib>And I'm</adlib>
    <theme topic="home"> And I'm Crooklyn's finest <adlib>Crooklyn's finest</adlib></theme> You
    rewind this, Bad Boy's behind this <adlib>Bad Boy's behind this</adlib></verse>



  <interlude artist="{uff and Biggie"> As we proceed to give you what you need <adlib>What?</adlib>
    <style type="repetition">9-5, motherfuckers <adlib>What?</adlib></style> Get live, motherfuckers
    As we proceed to give you what you need <adlib>What?</adlib>
    <theme topic="home"> East Coast, motherfuckers</theme> Bad Boy, motherfuckers <style
      type="repetition"> Get high, motherfuckers Get high, motherfuckers <adlib>Uh,
      uh</adlib></style>
    <theme topic="drugs">Smoke blunts, motherfuckers</theme>
    <adlib>Uh</adlib>
    <style type="repetition">Get high, motherfuckers <adlib>9-5, uh</adlib></style> Ready to die,
    motherfuckers <adlib>Uh</adlib>
    <style type="repetition"> 9-5, motherfuckers <adlib>Uh</adlib></style></interlude>


  <verse artist="Biggie"> I seen the light excite all the freaks Stack mad chips, spread love with
    my peeps Niggas wanna creep, gotta watch my back Think the Cognac and indo sack make me slack? I
    switches all that, cocksucker, <style type="collo">G's up</style>
    <style type="collo">One false move, get Swiss cheesed up</style> Clip to TEC, respect, I demand
    it Slip and break the 11th Commandment Thou shalt not fuck with nor see Poppa Feel a thousand
    deaths when I drop you I feel for you, like Chaka Khan, I'm the don <theme topic="sex"> Pussy
      when I want</theme>, <theme topic="money">Rolex on the arm</theme> You'll die slow but calm
    Recognize my face so there won't be no mistake So you know where to tell Jake, lame nigga Brave
    nigga, turned front page nigga <style type="allusion">Puff Daddy</style> flips daily <theme
      topic="drugs"> I smoke the blunts he sips on the Baileys On the rocks</theme>, <theme
      topic="violence">tote Glocks at christenings Hammer cock, in the fire position
    and</theme>—</verse>


  <interlude artist="Biggie">
    <style type="dialogue">Come here, come here <adlib>It ain't gotta be like that, B.I.G.</adlib>
      Open your fucking mouth, open your— <style type="repetition">Didn't I tell you don't fuck with
        me? <adlib>Come on, man</adlib> Huh? Didn't I tell you not to fuck with me? <adlib>Come on,
          man</adlib> Huh? <adlib>Come on, man Look at you now, huh? Come on, man</adlib></style>
      <theme topic="violence"> Can't talk with a gun in your mouth, huh?</theme></style> Bitch-ass
    nigga, what? Who shot ya?</interlude>

  <outro artist="Puffy Biggie"> To give you what you need <style type="repetition">9-5,
      motherfuckers</style> Get live, motherfuckers <theme topic="durgs">Get high,
      motherfuckers</theme>
    <adlib>Who shot ya?</adlib> Ready to die, motherfuckers, hah! As we proceed <adlib>Who shot
      ya?</adlib> To give you what you need <style type="repetition">9-5, motherfuckers</style> East
    Coast, motherfucker <adlib>Who shot ya?</adlib>
    <style type="repetition">West Coast, motherfuckers <adlib>Uh</adlib> West Coast, motherfuckers,
      hah!</style>
    <style type="repetition"> As we proceed to give you what you need As we proceed to give you what
      you need</style>
    <adlib>As we proceed to give you what you need</adlib>
    <style type="repetition"> Get live, motherfuckers Get live, motherfuckers <adlib>Get live,
        motherfuckers</adlib> 9-5, motherfuckers <adlib>9-5, motherfuckers</adlib>
      <theme topic="money"> Get money, motherfuckers</theme> As we proceed to give you what you need
        <adlib>As we proceed to give you what you need</adlib> Get live, motherfuckers <adlib>Get
        live, motherfuckers</adlib> 9-5, motherfuckers J.M., motherfuckers J.M.,
      motherfuckers</style> As we proceed To give you what you need 9-5</outro>
</song>
