<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
    [Verse 1]
    As I sit back relax, steam a blunt, sip a Becks
    Think about the sexy singers that I wanna sex
    I'd probably go to jail for fucking Patti LaBelle
    Ooh, Regina Belle, she'd probably do me swell
    Jasmine Guy was fly, Mariah Carey's kinda scary
    Wait a minute, what about my honey, Mary?
    Them jeans, they fitting like a glove
    I had a crush on you since Real Love, huh
    Hold your horses
    I'ma show you who the boss of intercourse is
    Sex, I'm taking no losses
    Even groups like SWV and TLC can't see B.I.G. with telepathy
    The recipe, a pinch of hardcore with a gun
    Pimpin' ain't easy, but it sure is fun
    When I bust my nuts I bust 'em one by one
    So what's the 4-1-1, hun?
    
    
    [Chorus]
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', I'm sayin')
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', I'm sayin')
    
    [Verse 2]
    I'll put Chanté Moore pussy in stitches
    I'll fuck RuPaul before I fuck them ugly-ass Xscape bitches
    You can 76 the 69, try 68
    Make Raven-Symoné call date rape
    Only 'cause I'm paid, I'm fucking all of Jade
    And my DJ Zhané, he likes it when they say
    "Everybody move your body"
    Got Whitney Houston boosting from Bobby
    As I bust the cherry of Monica and Terri
    Back shots to Chaka, I know that pussy hairy
    Sade, ooh, I know that pussy tight
    Smack Tina Turner give her flashbacks of Ike
    Smoke a stoge, fuckin' En Vogue because it's four of them
    Jimmy hats for Patra, I'm using all of them
    (What about Toni Braxton?)
    If that bitch give me action, guaranteed satisfaction
    
    [Chorus]
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', I'm sayin')
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
    Dreams of fuckin' an R&B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
    
    You might also like
    Flowers
    Miley Cyrus
    Shakira: Bzrp Music Sessions, Vol. 53
    Bizarrap & Shakira
    Bizarrap & Shakira - Shakira: Bzrp Music Sessions, Vol. 53 (English Translation)
    Genius English Translations
    
    [Outro]
    You know what I'm sayin', Tim, man?
    I ain't tryna diss the honeys
    You know what I'm sayin'? (I'm just playin', I'm sayin')
    I just be buggin', you know what I'm sayin'?
    I ain't tryna disrespect nobody, you know?
    I'm just buggin' out, you know? (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
    You know the flavor of the Junior M.A.F.I.A. clique
    Know what I'm sayin'?
    Buttnaked Tim Dawg in the motherfuckin' house
    I'm just playin' (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
    We're just havin' a little fun
    Ain't no harm done, B (I'm just playin', I'm sayin')
    But I would hit all of y'all
</song>
