<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../song_schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<song>

  <verse artist="Biggie">
    <theme topic="sex">As I sit back relax, steam a blunt, sip a Becks Think about the sexy singers
      that I wanna sex I'd probably go to jail for fucking <style type="allusion">Patti
        LaBelle</style> Ooh, <style type="allusion">Regina Belle,</style> she'd probably do me swell
      Jasmine Guy was fly, <style type="allusion">Mariah Carey's</style> kinda scary Wait a minute,
      what about my honey, Mary? Them jeans, they fitting like a glove I had a crush on you since
      Real Love, huh Hold your horses I'ma show you who the boss of intercourse is Sex, I'm taking
      no losses Even groups like <style type="allusion">SWV and TLC</style> can't see B.I.G. with
      telepathy The recipe, a pinch of hardcore with a gun Pimpin' ain't easy, but it sure is fun
      When I bust my nuts I bust 'em one by one So what's the 4-1-1, hun?</theme>
  </verse>



  <chorus artist="Biggie">
    <theme topic="sex">
      <style type="repetition">Dreams of fuckin' an R&amp;B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
        Dreams of fuckin' an R&amp;B bitch (I'm just playin', I'm sayin') Dreams of fuckin' an
        R&amp;B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin') Dreams of fuckin' an R&amp;B bitch (I'm
        just playin', I'm sayin')</style></theme>
  </chorus>


  <verse artist="Biggie">
    <theme topic="sex">I'll put <style type="allusion">Chanté Moore</style> pussy in stitches I'll
      fuck <style type="allusion">RuPaul</style> before I fuck them ugly-ass Xscape bitches You can
      76 the 69, try 68 Make <style type="allusion">Raven-Symoné </style>call date rape Only 'cause
      I'm paid, I'm fucking all of Jade And my <style type="allusion">DJ Zhané</style>, he likes it
      when they say "Everybody move your body" Got <style type="allusion">Whitney
      Houston</style>boosting from <style type="allusion">Bobby</style> As I bust the cherry of
        <style type="allusion">Monica and Terri</style> Back shots to <style type="allusion"
        >Chaka</style>, I know that pussy hairy Sade, ooh, I know that pussy tight Smack <style
        type="allusion">Tina Turner</style> give her flashbacks of <style type="allusion"
        >Ike</style> Smoke a stoge, fuckin' En Vogue because it's four of them <style
        type="allusion"> Jimmy hats for Patra</style>, I'm using all of them (What about <style
        type="allusion">Toni Braxton?</style>) If that bitch give me action, guaranteed
      satisfaction</theme>
  </verse>

  <chorus artist="Biggie">
    <style type="repetition"> Dreams of fuckin' an R&amp;B bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')
      Dreams of fuckin' an R&amp;B bitch (I'm just playin', I'm sayin') Dreams of fuckin' an R&amp;B
      bitch (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin') Dreams of fuckin' an R&amp;B bitch (I'm just playin',
      but I'm sayin')</style>
  </chorus>




  <outro artist="Biggie"> You know what I'm sayin', Tim, man? I ain't tryna diss the honeys You know
    what I'm sayin'?<style type="repetition">(I'm just playin', I'm sayin')</style>
    <style type="collo"> I just be buggin'</style>, you know what I'm sayin'? I ain't tryna
    disrespect nobody, you know? <style type="collo"> I'm just buggin' out</style>, you know? <style
      type="repetition">(I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')</style> You know the flavor of the <style
      type="allusion">Junior M.A.F.I.A. clique</style> Know what I'm sayin'? <style type="allusion">
      Buttnaked Tim Dawg </style>in the motherfuckin' house <style type="allusion"> I'm just playin'
      (I'm just playin', but I'm sayin')</style> We're just havin' a little fun Ain't no harm done,
    B <style type="allusion">(I'm just playin', I'm sayin')</style>
    <theme topic="sex">But I would hit all of y'all</theme></outro>
</song>
